[♪ upbeat music plays]
[panting]
[pants]
Someone is bound to notice.
We should get back.
I can't see that happening, Güneş.
[panting]
How did we get to this point, Deniz?
Should I stop?
-[door slams]
-[♪ music ends]
Who was that?
reminder.
2023 TRENDS "LACE"
A FEW WEEKS AGO
[person]
Do you remember what love was like?
There were ways of living it.
There was the thrill of discovering it.
Love was like getting lost
in a foreign language.
It was knowing that the real gem
was hidden in the moment.
It was discovering him in the details.
Love was the inability
to describe a feeling.
At times,
love was a miracle you had to fight for.
Ultimately, it was a duel that could only
be won by those who lived that miracle.
It was opening your heart to hear
the most beautiful melody in the world.
It was fitting life into a smile.
Love was to see with your heart.
You used to embrace life as it came.
As if nothing were a miracle.
Then, love would appear
to make life the miracle it truly is.
[chuckles] Are you actually
quoting my own article back to me?
Listen, Güneş.
[chuckles] 157,000 people
have shared your article.
I get it. You're trying
to talk me out of it.
Oh, no. The thing is,
I can't believe the author is on her way
to break up with him right now.
I've made up my mind, Beren.
It's not working out. You know that, too.
I don't know.
I guess I feel it's partly my fault.
Now, it seems like I made you think twice
about this guy by saying
that things seemed different with Deniz.
Uh-uh. What are you talking about?
I decided to break up with Boran.
It has nothing to do with you, okay?
Well, what about Mr. Alpha?
Could it have something to do with Deniz?
You hesitated.
Come on, admit it.
You still have a thing for Deniz.
Fine, I do.
Every time I pick up my phone,
I see people asking about Mr. Alpha.
Oh, yeah.
You can't say you broke up, right?
It's insane, isn't it?
Being an influencer and having your life
so bridled by your love affair, right?
So weird.
[Güneş] Actually,
I was just your typical magazine editor.
But Deniz used to loathe Instagram.
You know, the whole influencer thing,
having followers.
He said I could do whatever I wanted
as long as I kept him out of it.
So, on one of our vacations,
I posted a photo of us hugging,
showing only his shoulders and back.
And instead of using his name,
I tagged him as Mr. Alpha.
My first vacation with Mr. Alpha.
My third date with Mr. Alpha.
The more I shared these intimate moments,
the more curious my followers became
about who Deniz was.
We broke up six months ago.
It was complicated.
I stopped posting.
I ended it, so don't get carried away
when I say complicated.
Anyway, I met Boran a few months ago.
[sighs] Now, it's time
for a breakup conversation with him.
I'm so sorry.
What did you say?
I wanted to know who you are here for.
Boran.
Boran gave me this address.
Güneş.
Oh. He looks so happy! Wish me luck.
Boran.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
You look amazing.
Thank you.
-How are you?
-Fine.
I hope to keep it that way.
Boran, why did we meet here?
Is this place yours as well?
[laughs] How did you guess?
We seem to have a habit
of meeting at places you own.
We used upcycled materials
in the construction.
So, we cut costs
and minimized our environmental impact.
By using natural stone and wood,
in addition to upcycled material,
we wanted to create
a sustainable structure.
And I believe we did
an excellent job with that.
[phone ringing]
-Hakan, would you please continue?
-Sure.
[Deniz] What's the matter, Umay?
I understand you have a nickname
for your mystery man gig, Deniz.
Or should I refer to you as Mr. Alpha?
[scoffs] Who did you hear that from?
It's you. I knew it as soon as I saw you.
The main question is,
why haven't I heard it from you, Deniz?
Since when am I supposed to keep you
updated on my past love affairs? Come on!
So, you were in love?
[sighs]
It's over, finished.
What are you getting at?
Deniz. You told me
that it ended six months ago.
-And?
-Look at this.
She posted it a few weeks ago.
So what? She posts whatever she wants.
-She writes--
-Oh. So, you know she writes.
In that case, there's no point in me
telling you about her article,
"Remember Love." Right, Deniz?
Can you calm down?
People are looking at us.
I don't care.
You are being really annoying
for no reason here.
For no reason? Really?
Stop pissing me off, Deniz.
You're not even on social media.
Where did you see this post then?
Huh? Who?
Was it Hakan? Did he tell you
to reconsider your options?
What else did he say?
What did he tell you?
You are so touchy about everything.
Make sure you know the facts
before throwing a tantrum.
If I meant anything to you,
you would have told me, Deniz.
It's all very clear and quite easy
to understand. Thanks.
-And I'm not finished with you. Got it?
-Oh, man. Look…
Bro, what's her beef with me?
I'm in the doghouse myself. You just saw.
-What was all that about?
-Everything was fine,
but it seems she thrives on arguments.
What else? Beats me. [sighs]
[chattering]
What's the occasion?
There seems to be a birthday every week.
Aren't they adorable? Look at them.
[chuckles] Hello.
I mean. They are adorable, but…
why did we meet here, Boran?
[sighs] Um…
Güneş, I need to talk to you.
I also have a question for you.
Well, I needed a word with you, too.
I just don't know
if this is the right place.
I've been thinking for the past few weeks,
and I've struggled to decide
how to say it.
-[party popper pops]
-[both exclaim]
Pops, you were too early. Not now.
Why did you do that?
-Um, Güneş.
-Huh?
I want our life to be filled
with celebrations as well.
Will you grow old with me?
What?
Yes.
I mean…
-Will you marry me?
-[♪ string music plays]
[crowd applauds]
This…
Well, you really took me by surprise.
Um, so? Don't you think
a surprise proposal is much better?
No. Um, it's-- It's not.
Isn't it way too early for us
to tie the knot?
Listen, let's tie the knot.
We'll work through all our issues.
I know we can make it work.
I want you to understand how serious I am,
Güneş.
But do you have any idea what I want?
Here I am, asking you.
Isn't this what you want too?
[exhales] Boran--
Look, my grandmother is watching.
Seeing this in her lifetime
was all she ever wished for.
-Grandma.
-Indeed.
I'm waiting for your answer. Go on.
[Boran] Come on.
You've put me in such a tight spot
right now.
Okay. Aren't you going to put on the ring?
Güneş.
All right. I'll take the ring.
But we need to discuss it
in detail later, okay?
Okay. But you will wear it, right?
Yes. Okay. Yes. [chuckles]
-[cheering] Bravo.
-[Boran] Yes! That's it.
-Stop that!
-[Boran laughs]
[♪ music continues]
[no dialogue audible]
[Beren] How did it go?
Did you break up with him?
I think I kind of agreed to marry him.
What?
Well, I didn't say yes, but the ring…
The thing is I put the ring on,
so he wouldn't lose face
in front of his grandma.
Um, you put the ring on?
Yes.
But I must have a word with him
when I return the ring,
because right now
everything is a huge mess.
If only this event were over.
Or maybe it shouldn't be over.
I really need to get hammered.
What event? Whe… Where are you?
I'm at the "Cities of the Future" event.
Check out my collab post.
Oh, hold on.
I'm checking it right now. One sec.
Güneş Güner
[gasps] Güneş, you're unbelievable.
You're still wearing the ring.
Yes, I am because this ring
won't come off, Beren.
I can't take it off. It's stuck.
Ugh!
I forgot about it and posted the pic.
I realized it later, but it was too late.
Is it that obvious?
Look. People are asking
if the ring is from Mr. Alpha.
[sighs]
Nothing to do with Deniz. Not now.
Beren.
I have to go.
CITIES OF THE FUTURE
[sighs]
Please serve the lady first.
Thank you. The gentleman can have it.
Absolutely not.
She is not just a good editor
but also a renowned influencer.
I'm no match.
This gentleman is
the famous architect Deniz Derenoğlu.
He is delivering the opening speech today.
That slipped my mind
before coming to this event.
Where is your Mr. Alpha?
I don't know.
Where is he?
Even if he's here, we'll never know
who he is, right?
Hmm.
I was unaware of the schedule
and the speakers before coming here.
You don't need to leave
just because I'm here.
I shouldn't stop you from doing your job.
[Güneş scoffs, laughs]
[continues laughing]
All right.
I'm sorry, but what's so funny?
Do my job?
Seriously?
I'm totally cool with it.
What are you cool with?
I'm curious.
What are you cool about? Me being here?
Me being an influencer?
Remember, we broke up
because I'm an influencer, Deniz.
I'll get you both something stronger, sir.
No, thanks.
I was about to leave anyway.
-[knocks on door]
-[Deniz] Güneş, open the door, will you?
6 MONTHS AGO
What will it take to knock
some sense into you?
I told you on the phone, Deniz.
I had no idea that the ad was for
your rival company when I sent the post.
Hmm.
You're leaning on my shoulder in the photo
to promote a happy future
in Argah Residence, is that it?
They have the right to use
my posts for their projects.
It's my job. What can I do? It's work!
Do as you please, but why drag me into it?
You promised
you would never do that again.
I signed a contract stating
that the ad must feature Mr. Alpha.
I had to. I was obligated.
What else could I do?
Oh, you had to, eh?
Are you kidding me?
Our blown-up photos are everywhere.
I never thought it would
be such a big campaign.
I tried to tell you as soon as
I found out, but you never listened.
You were never interested in my work.
I get it. You thought I wouldn't find out.
I saw it when I was stuck in traffic.
Is that better, you think?
-Did you decide to betray my trust?
-Stop being ridiculous. Enough already!
What's the big deal?
No one can see your face.
Do you even realize that?
How could I know it's your rival?
Well, I can. Isn't that enough?
You drive me up the wall.
That photo will be on display
at the construction site for months.
Is our life just about your posts?
Someone will find out it's me
sooner or later. What then?
What do you think my company will say?
Think about it for once.
I had no idea the campaign
would be so big, Deniz.
[sighs] Güneş, listen.
-We agreed that this job would hurt us…
-[sighs]
…and you promised not to post again.
Didn't you make a promise? Answer me.
It was part of the contract
I had already signed.
What don't you understand?
You can't even keep your promises to me,
and you expect us to plan a future.
What are you saying?
What does that even mean?
It means if you don't change,
a happy future like the one
in those photos is impossible.
Is that clear enough?
All right. Fine, Deniz.
Let's not have a future.
Forget it. Here. I'll delete everything.
Let's finish this
if it's that easy for you.
You… You really don't want me
doing this anyway. Just admit it.
What are you talking about? Share
whatever you like! This has nothing to do
-with you being an influencer.
-Yeah, sure.
I said I didn't want to be
in those photos anymore.
I told you many times.
I asked you not to use me.
Do whatever you want,
just leave me out of it.
What did you do? You promised me!
Who fucking cares if my career
is ruined by your post?
I'm now a model for an ad
on my rival's construction site.
So fucking what if my career
and reputation are gone?
Are you listening to me, Güneş?
You've broken my trust.
Do you understand that?
[scoffs] Let's assume I broke my promise.
Was it one post that ruined your career?
You're still talking about work.
I can't believe
you're still talking about it.
I don't care about careers, Güneş.
But this has ruined us.
[door opens]
[Deniz] Güneş.
[♪ piano music plays]
Deniz.
You're doing well. Look at you.
You kept your job.
Still the greatest architect around.
We didn't break up because of my career.
It was a trust issue.
[scoffs]
If you had trusted me and stood by me,
there would be no need for Mr. Alpha.
Maybe none of this would have happened.
Maybe if you hadn't dragged me into
your job, we wouldn't have had a problem.
How about that?
I don't need you for my articles,
and I'm not in the mood to listen to you.
Why don't you talk
to your audience tonight?
Why don't you stick around?
[sighs]
Who knows, you might hear some stuff
you could use in your articles.
You're right.
I made a mistake by sincerely
sharing my feelings back then.
[presenter] Let's give a round of applause
to the acclaimed architect Deniz Derenoğlu
as he steps onto the stage
for the opening speech.
[Deniz] Thank you all so much. Welcome.
We have gathered
to discuss a sustainable future.
While this is a broad topic,
I believe we can reshape it
by learning from the past.
Or, by remembering the past.
[phone buzzing]
[sighs]
Sis!
Did you make up with Deniz?
Oh, you saw the ring too?
Yes. I'm so happy for you, Sis.
I have good news for you too.
Honey, it's not what it looks like.
Hold on. What news?
Were you accepted?
-Yes, I was.
-Really?
I can't believe it.
So, you're going to the US?
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
-I'm so happy.
-[sighs]
Um, why aren't you excited?
I got accepted,
but not with a full scholarship.
It's very expensive.
Listen. Don't tell Mom and Dad.
Let's not get their hopes up.
It's okay, don't worry about it.
I will take care of it.
I'll find a way. I'll figure it out.
Don't think about it now.
Okay, but please
don't worry about it either.
I didn't call to upset you.
Keep it between us for now.
Okay, I understand.
Please don't worry. I'll take care of it.
Just trust me.
It's your dream school, remember that.
Celebrate your accomplishment!
Just tell me how much you need to enroll,
okay?
By the way, don't tell Mom and Dad
that I'm back together with Deniz.
The ring is not from Deniz.
It's from Boran.
Boran! Really, Sis?
-Yes.
-Oh.
We both have things to sort out.
[sighs, scoffs]
Oh! [winces]
[sighs]
[knocks on door]
Yes.
Deniz Derenoğlu?
[alarm beeping]
[Güneş]
Deniz Derenoğlu no longer lives here.
Well, this is the address.
This package has been waiting
to be delivered for months.
-Honestly, I can't carry it down.
-What am I supposed to do with it?
What are you doing?
I'm telling you, he doesn't live here.
You can't leave it here.
Where are you going? What the heck?
What am I supposed to do with it?
[groans]
[sighs]
Jerk.
[grunts]
[sighs]
Pervin
You're going to Cappadocia!
[Pervin] So. What do you say?
I really don't understand, Pervin.
What don't you understand, honey?
Don't you know what a donation is?
-A donation.
-I know what a donation is.
By whom? Why me? I mean,
who donates a house to a stranger?
Not just to you.
She left it to you and Deniz.
Eh? The lawyer asked me whether Mr. Alpha
was your true love or a publicity stunt.
I assured them that you two
were indeed lovers.
-No worries.
-Pervin.
I wonder if she was moved by your piece
on "Remember Love"?
Speaking of love, where is Deniz?
Love. Love.
[laughs] Cutie pie.
Where is Deniz? Where is he?
Why isn't he picking up my calls?
Pervin.
Deniz and I broke up.
Who approved this, dear?
Excuse me?
This isn't a decision you both can make
by yourselves, my dear.
He will check if your love is genuine.
Hold hands and go together, hand in hand.
Why should we go? For what?
Because she left you a house.
That's why.
Hold on. I have a question.
How much do you think this house is worth?
I mean, will it cover tuition fees
at an American college?
I can't say for sure.
But this is the figure
they want for taxes.
What?
How in the world am I going
to pay that amount?
Weren't you the one who encouraged me
to become an influencer?
You said I would make a lot of money.
Do you realize I haven't earned anything
close to that yet?
Honey, don't worry about paying anything.
Just focus on earning.
Be patient and calm down. Take it slow.
-Hey, you already have a house. Huh?
-[sighs]
Sell it and pay for your sister's tuition.
Get back together with Deniz.
Let love win. Huh?
Go to Cappadocia and post a photo
like true lovers.
-What harm will it do?
-Fine.
Okay, but…
Deniz will never agree to this.
You know that.
He will never do it.
Talk to him, honey.
Just have a chat.
You love each other, and I know it.
-Oh!
-[sighs]
Your story about meeting him
was incredible. It was so moving.
I was truly touched.
The one with you on the ferry.
What was it like?
Hold on, I'll look for it.
[ferry horn honks]
[♪ gentle music plays]
[alarm sounding]
-Miss. Miss!
-Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Ma'am, what are you doing?
You can't do that!
[Deniz] Jump.
[♪ romantic music plays]
Hop on. I'll get you.
[staff] Ma'am, the ferry is about to
leave. What you're doing is very reckless.
[ferry horn honks]
You really did catch me.
-I always do. I never miss.
-[grunts]
Maybe you should let go now?
You're the one who's holding me.
[laughs] I'm so, so sorry. Um.
Anyway. Thank you.
Aren't you going to buy me something?
Tea and simit?
Deal.
-[chuckles]
-[thumps]
-It's rocking a bit. Careful.
-It does that.
Okay.
All right. I'll talk to Deniz.
That's it.
[line ringing]
[Deniz] You're brave. You didn't hesitate.
[Güneş] You can't say you've lived
unless you take risks
and believe in destiny and luck.
[Deniz] Are you a writer?
An editor.
Both stunning and articulate.
Behaves like an alpha male
and has a flair for fashion.
Uh-oh.
Is it the jacket?
Your sweater. Lilac.
It's a color I like.
Wow, that's an impressive pickup line!
How do you do it?
I mean in a literary sense,
considering you're an editor.
I get it, but I don't know
if I'm still an editor or not.
Am I late for work?
Or did the alpha male save the day
by helping me catch the ferry?
You'll be in Bostancı in fifteen minutes,
tops.
Beşiktaş.
This is the Beşiktaş ferry.
It's the Bostancı ferry.
Beşiktaş.
Beşik--
Am I on the wrong ferry?
Why did you help me on this ferry?
It's not my fault? I just helped.
Oh!
I'm definitely fired this time.
I'm fired for sure.
Don't worry.
I'll help you make it on time.
Yeah, sure. In İstanbul traffic? How?
[♪ romantic music plays]
It's breathtaking!
Absolutely.
Very.
Do you prefer the ferry or the motorcycle?
It doesn't matter as long as
I have someone with me.
Did you hear what I said?
Did you say something?
I can hardly hear with the helmet on.
Oh, dear.
Can I trust you?
Enjoy the experience.
Aren't you supposed
to have another helmet?
There was no reason to have one.
Aren't you going to tell me your name?
What do you need my name for?
What name do I save your number under?
Güneş, like the sun emoji.
By the way,
I'll be done here in an hour or two.
My meeting might finish early.
Great.
Meet me at the pier in three hours then.
-Don't miss the ferry.
-[chuckles]
Will you ever ask for my name?
[clicks tongue] I'll call you Alpha.
Catch.
[sighs]
Okay, people. Our concept is diversity.
Diversity.
Sustainability.
Sustainability and diversity in fashion.
And most importantly,
how love connects to these concepts.
Love always sells.
It always has, and it always will.
Right? Now…
[♪ uplifting music plays]
[no audible dialogue]
[Pervin] …for sure. I mean…
[♪ music continues]
We expect this from Güneş.
Right, Güneş?
-Hello, Güneş?
-[♪ music fades]
-Güneş, dear?
-Huh?
You've got something in the pipeline,
right?
Oh, I have a feeling it's going
to be very, very good.
But don't forget, folks,
diversity is the key word.
Let's make this issue shine, okay?
Here, these are for you, Mr. Erhan.
You can take a look if you want.
They will also be e-mailed to you.
I mean, I'm really buzzing.
I expect the same enthusiasm
from all of you.
[ferry horn honks]
[footsteps running]
[Güneş] Wait, wait, wait.
Oh no!
I'm late. Darn.
I can't believe I missed it. [sighs]
Are you disappointed that you missed
the ferry or me? Which one? Be honest.
All right. But you first.
How long have you been standing here,
watching people get on and off the ferries
to meet me?
I just got here.
It took a while
to find a lilac-colored helmet.
No sweat.
We weren't taking the ferry anyway.
Meaning?
If we weren't going to take the ferry,
why did I race all the way here?
I suppose you're not the romantic type.
No, I like romance.
I love it, but I can't stand traffic.
All right then, let's go.
This way.
Why do you take the ferry
when you have such a cool motorcycle?
Let's say it was a hunch.
Will you help me?
Sure.
There.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
[♪ uplifting music plays]
-Hello.
-Welcome.
I'm here to see Deniz Derenoğlu.
Let me check to see if he's here.
[receptionist] Is Mr. Deniz in his office?
There is Mr. Deniz.
Why aren't you answering your phone?
I was on the motorcycle.
You wouldn't come here for no reason.
Is something wrong?
I'm not fond of talking to you,
so I wouldn't be here
if it weren't important.
Oh.
I'll tell you if you're ready to listen.
Go ahead then.
The thing is…
Deniz, look at me, will you?
Stop acting like a child.
If you don't want to listen, just tell me,
and I'll leave.
I'm all ears, Güneş.
I'm here to ask a favor.
By the way, a package was delivered to you
at your old address.
It's been over six months, Deniz.
Why haven't you updated it?
I have.
Not immediately,
but it's been a few months though.
Uh-huh.
To be honest, it was only a few weeks ago.
I thought so.
There must be a mistake.
I haven't ordered anything lately, though.
Didn't you feel the urge to sneak a peek?
Should I have?
No, I didn't.
I thought you might have ordered it
a while ago.
I didn't touch it.
Were you worried
it might bring back memories?
[Umay] Deniz.
Am I interrupting?
[Deniz] No. No.
You wanted to ask me something.
I'm interrupting.
I'll take care of it. No problem.
All right.
[receptionist] This is for you.
When will she let us be, Deniz?
-She already has.
-Really?
Come on, Deniz.
I saw how she looked at the helmet.
I looked through Güneş's articles
while waiting for the coffee.
Hmm.
Here's the deal.
You might still think
about Güneş occasionally.
But I'm not having it.
Call me when she's out
of your life for good.
Okay?
Enjoy.
Thanks.
[sighs]
[friend] It looks like
you've struck gold in life, girl.
The opportunity to cover
your sister's tuition,
take a long vacation,
and experience true love.
What more could you wish for?
-But there's a catch.
-She refuses to listen.
We need to convince the lawyer
that Deniz and I are a couple.
Sure, go talk to Deniz.
He can pretend you two are still together
and convince the lawyer. So what?
Sure, but he also has to deal
-with his new unruly lover.
-Ugh!
-Don't talk like that, Özgen.
-What do you expect, honey?
I'll deal with it.
I'll find a way.
I'll go alone to talk to the lawyer.
I will also go to Cappadocia
to see the house.
Hold on…
Are you going to Cappadocia
to see the house, or is it just escapism?
I don't understand.
I mean, I can't tell if it's an attempt
to avoid talking to Deniz
or to stop herself from opening that box.
Open the box already. See for yourself.
-Enough.
-[Özgen laughs]
Enough. [scoffs] I've had it up to here
with box metaphors.
-Okay. Fine.
-Pfft. Okay.
So, are you actually going to Cappadocia?
Of course, I am. What else should I do?
I can't afford the tuition fee right now.
Gosh.
I wonder what lies ahead for her
while she sits here making plans.
-Enough, Özgen.
-[laughs]
-Okay, sorry. Forgive me. I apologize.
-[Güneş] Enough already.
I can't help saying something, though.
Let's keep the box closed
so we can keep staring at it.
Güneş, for God's sake,
please open that box now.
-No, I won't.
-Why don't you?
I won't.
I see. All right.
Opening the box will cause Güneş
to confront the past.
-I'm sure that's the reason.
-No.
It has nothing to do with that.
What are you suggesting?
If so, then why aren't we opening it?
Let's just do it.
Because it's not mine.
Pfft. Jesus.
Deniz belongs to someone else now.
-You're being ridiculous.
-[chuckles] What?
Don't be ridiculous, seriously.
Stop bothering me.
For one thing,
there's still a connection between them.
Never mind her, girl.
Can you give me a recap?
I'm interested in the close contact
and intimacy. I want to hear it all again.
I never talked about intimacy.
Well. But--
Honey,
that's exactly what you've been implying.
You've been staring at the box,
talking about your love affair.
Tell me I'm wrong.
[Özgen]
And I'll repeat myself if necessary.
Your paths keep crossing
professionally and personally.
It's like a movie.
All you say is love! Where is love?
Show me. There is no love. It's over.
In fact, everything to do
with Deniz is over.
No doubt. I am sure about that.
Whatever you say.
Yeah, sure, but what about
the elephant in the room, Güneş?
Huh?
Honey, let's open the box.
Please, I'm begging you.
My heart is pounding.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm not touching it.
-Look, she's losing it.
-You're so stubborn.
I'm losing my mind.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[Deniz] Ege.
Are they at it again?
Never mind. It doesn't matter.
I'm going to have a word with your father.
This is not on.
You could try,
but there's no point when he's drunk.
[sighs]
Were you out there all night?
What a relief.
I could barely hear my thoughts.
What were you thinking of?
I was trying to decide whether I should
show you Güneş's last post.
Go on, show me.
It seems she has moved on.
There may be someone new.
No, that photo is from an event.
You drink too much as well.
You haven't recovered from Güneş.
You look for happiness in others.
Stop it.
This is no way to live.
Kiddo, you're just seven years old.
What do you know about life?
[sighs] Oh.
Umay and I had another argument.
I think it's over this time.
It's for the best, bro.
You drink too much of this stuff.
Pull yourself together already.
Here.
I have one pleasure in life.
-Leave me alone.
-[scoffs]
Cheers.
[sighs]
-I saw Güneş.
-Where?
Where did you see her?
Did she ask about me?
We talked briefly.
What did she say? Has she missed me?
We couldn't talk much.
Why? What did you do again?
Stop wasting her time,
or I won't be your friend anymore.
I take it you didn't
get much sleep last night.
Isn't it time for you to rest?
Go lay down over there.
Isn't it time you woke up, Deniz?
Ege, kid.
Go lie down now, or I'll put you
back on the doorstep where I found you.
I'm just looking out for you.
Umay isn't your type, Deniz.
You're about to lose Güneş for good.
You're still young.
I'm sure you'll understand me better
as you grow older.
If you understood how you were with Güneş,
you would know what I mean.
My parents have worn me out.
I can't handle an argument
with you right now.
Okay, I hear you. Go on then,
get some rest. Quick.
[sighs, huffs] Fine.
I'm going to rest my eyes.
If they come, please don't carry me
next door to my bed like a baby, okay?
I won't forgive you.
Seriously? What's wrong with that?
I said I don't want to argue.
Fine. Get some rest now.
[sighs]
She was wearing a pink dress,
just like on our first date.
[sighs]
[sighs] Mmm.
But I didn't have much to say.
[Güneş] The woman told me everything.
She even described you.
Actually, she warned me about
the problems we might run into.
2 YEARS AGO
Visiting a fortune teller
on our first date
is something that never occurred to me.
She's a psychic, not a fortune teller.
Fine.
Do you really believe
those psychics and fortune tellers?
Hmm.
I believe in us.
So, right now,
I prefer to savor my margarita
and pretend I didn't hear what she said.
Come on. What exactly did she say?
I'm curious. Please tell me.
I'll tell you when the time comes.
You won't find out until then.
Oh, really?
What's going to happen then?
Huh?
We embark on a long journey.
One that will change our lives.
Deniz.
Deniz, do you hear me?
[grunts]
Güneş.
[knocks on door]
-Boran?
-Güneş, I'm sorry.
I've thought about it, and I realize
I put you in an awkward position.
I know. You're right.
So, these are for you.
Um. I wish you had called.
Uh… You're right.
I should have called,
but I wanted to talk in person.
I wanted to see you…
[chuckles] …to see your beautiful face.
Listen, Güneş.
-Wear the ring when you feel ready.
-[door closes]
Don't if you'd rather not.
Honestly.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
DENİZ DERENOĞLU
İSTANBUL
[Boran] I don't want to push you.
I just want you to be happy.
-You are okay, right?
-Uh-huh.
Um. I don't want these to wilt,
so I'll put them in water.
Is that all right?
I have something to tell you.
From now on, we'll do things your way,
okay?
[chuckles]
[phone buzzes]
What the…
[sighs]
[huffs]
-Hello.
-Deniz, how are you, sweetie?
You never return my calls
but when I saw the photo,
I wanted to congratulate you, dear.
What?
You made up with Güneş.
I knew it.
I knew it all along.
You are the perfect match.
I hope Cappadocia will do you good.
May your new house bring you blessings.
What? New house?
I took care of your reservations.
You will receive the check-in link soon.
Oh, you know what? I knew.
I could feel it.
Güneş keeps talking about your breakup,
yet she can't hide her feelings.
I know when I see true love.
-I know all about love. [chuckles]
-What?
-Is Güneş in love with someone?
-[laughs] Oh, Deniz. Come on, admit it.
You love hearing someone say
that Güneş loves you.
Just be honest.
All right, sweetheart.
I have an idea,
but I wanted to discuss it with you first.
Fine, let's talk. I'm listening.
You know how everyone
is dying to see your face.
I say let's make it happen in Cappadocia.
Let's reveal Mr. Alpha
to all the followers!
What do you think, Deniz?
Pervin, what are you talking about?
I really don't get it.
Güneş writes an article
about the house in Cappadocia.
And then, she can post a photo
like the one she shared today
but one where your face is seen.
Telling everyone, "This is Mr. Alpha."
What do you think?
It's phenomenal, right? It's huge!
So you're saying Güneş
posted a photo of Mr. Alpha,
and she's in love?
Where the hell is it?
[sighs]
Who the hell is this?
Check in and get your boarding pass.
Boran.
Fancy going to Cappadocia?
[Pervin] Deniz, darling.
What about it?
Shall we show them your face?
All right.
Let's reveal my face.
COMPLETE CHECK-IN
GÜNEŞ GÜNER - Deniz Derenoğlu