reminder.
I'm late. I'm late again.
I'm going to miss my flight.
-[phone buzzes]
-[huffs]
REMINDER: FLIGHT TO CAPPADOCIA
14:00
My bag? Where…
Is my bag in there?
Hey! Can't you hear me?
Taxi.
Deniz, can't you hear me?
-I'm telling you I'm running late.
-Oh, that's a surprise.
Please call me a taxi.
I'm busy getting ready.
I will take you to the airport.
-[Güneş] Hmm.
-Mm-hmm.
Then hold on.
You earned this.
Earned what?
-Uh-oh.
-[chuckles]
Mister? Where's the Alpha?
[inhales sharply]
Then please allow me to thank you…
properly. We have time.
-No, because I'm really late.
-Listen to me.
Trust me, will you?
-Just trust me.
-Deniz, I haven't finished packing yet.
-Will you let go?
-I won't.
No way. First, fly with me,
and then I'll make sure
you catch all your flights. I promise.
-[chuckles] Oh, really?
-Don't worry. Mm-hmm.
-I said no. Let go. [chuckles]
-Are you serious?
No chance.
Listen.
If you miss this flight, I promise
I'll make sure you catch the next one.
-[kisses]
-Not happening.
-Seriously?
-Uh-huh.
[kisses]
Think it over and let me know.
I'll be waiting for you down here.
[kisses] Okay?
[kissing]
[Güneş sighs]
-Fine.
-Hmm.
We'll take the motorbike again.
Yes.
Yes, the motorbike it is.
[♪ romantic music playing]
[music continues]
[Beren] Psst.
[Beren snaps fingers]
Did you see the comments
about Mr. Alpha under the photo?
I did,
but I can't bring myself to read them.
I regret what I did.
I literally lied to all my followers.
What about poor Boran? [sighs]
What's his take on this charade?
-I don't know.
-[Beren] Gosh!
Listen to her. Boran doesn't get
half the sympathy strangers get.
Well, it seemed like a solution at first.
I mean, no one has ever seen
Mr. Alpha anyway.
I thought I could go
and acquire the house with Boran.
We wouldn't even need
to pretend to be lovers.
Oh! Oh, I'm losing it.
First, she puts on the ring
to keep his grandma happy.
Now she says she's taking Boran
to acquire the house. [chuckles]
[scoffs] What the heck, Beren?
I posted it on a whim.
By the time I gathered my thoughts,
it was too late.
-[scoffs]
-And this is your rational self now?
Absolutely not. Am I happy?
No. And I'm clueless about what to do.
If you think about it,
things don't look that bad.
Hear me out.
You're going to sell that house
and pay for Ayça's tuition.
Um, I mean, maybe if you tell Boran,
he might even chip in. Won't he?
What am I supposed to tell him?
"Come with me to Cappadocia
and tell everyone you're Mr. Alpha"?
What will I do in Cappadocia? Tell me.
Honey, you'll be taking a free vacation.
Plus, you get the house for free.
I mean,
don't be such a drama queen about it.
[sighs] I need to talk to Boran.
I don't get this relationship. Honestly.
What's so difficult about breaking up
with a man you don't even love that much?
Why in the world would he propose
to someone he hasn't even slept with?
-Oh, is this the Middle Ages or what?
-Oh! [scoffs] Men.
-There are great men too.
-Let's say he proposed.
-Why is she wearing the ring? Why?
-[shushes]
[shushes]
Gosh!
I regret telling both of you any of this.
Listen to me. Stop talking to us
and sort things out with Boran. [laughs]
Shut up! Enough. This is no place
to talk about this stuff! Zip it.
[Özgen] It's good we talked about it now.
We would still be talking about it
at your wedding otherwise. [laughs]
[laughs]
-At least the ring is off. [laughs]
-[laughing] Exactly.
I must talk to Boran urgently.
You have something much more urgent to do.
Finishing that article for the magazine.
-Oh! And I have that too.
-[Özgen chuckles]
Oh, yeah.
Maybe I should write about
what I've been through…
Like Deniz told me to.
[Özgen laughing]
-[Beren] Geez. Oh, no.
-What?
-Cough up. [laughs]
-Come on!
What are you doing?
How much was it?
-[Beren] Here.
-[Özgen] Was it 200?
-Oh, that's not much. [laughs]
-[Beren] Yes, it was 200. Beat it.
-[sighs]
-Hold on now.
Did you bet on how many times
I would mention Deniz?
[laughing] Stop that.
She hasn't a clue. Cough up.
I don't believe you.
[Hakan] Can you believe it?
[Deniz] What?
Güneş, man. Geez.
Posting a photo in another man's arms
as if it were you.
Look, I've got enough on my mind
as it is, so back off.
What's on your mind, bro?
Numbers.
Like, can we make this work or not?
Work what?
The chain stores, Hakan.
Deniz, are you okay?
We just shook hands.
The guys haven't even left the building,
and here you are, racking your brain.
Chill, man. I will take care of
the construction site. We got this.
We need something.
Something to outdo our rivals.
When I visit London,
I will visit some stores
and prepare a feasibility report for you.
What does that mean?
Am I not going to London?
You're going to Cappadocia, bro.
You said you checked in.
No, man.
I got carried away back there.
I'm not going. It's pointless.
You got carried away seeing Güneş
in another man's arms, right?
-Hakan, enough already.
-[laughs]
Well, if you're so pumped up about it,
you should go.
Love makes a man jealous. Look at me.
I wish I were in love and felt that way.
-[sighs]
-[phone ringing]
Damn.
What's the matter, Ege?
In trouble at school again?
What?
-What is it?
-Where are you?
Okay. Wait there.
-What?
-It's nothing.
-Should I come with you?
-No, no.
Ege.
Here comes my Güneş.
What are you doing here?
Is something wrong?
How did you get here?
I got off the school bus with Pelin.
I left her at her house and walked here
to see you, Güneş.
Wow.
So, your parents don't know you're here?
Let's keep them out of this, Güneş.
I don't want to cause another argument
for no reason.
Do they still argue a lot?
They argue a lot.
I need a loving environment to grow up in.
-Speaking of love…
-Hmm.
Deniz broke up with that girl.
I think we should call your mother.
Let's tell her you'll be late
so she doesn't worry.
No need.
I called Deniz.
He's coming to pick me up.
Well, look at you, clever boy.
How did you think of calling Deniz?
Hmm.
-Um.
-Hmm?
-Pelin is a year older than me.
-Yeah.
-She's this much taller than me.
-[Güneş] Who is this Pelin?
Tell me. Is she beautiful?
[Deniz] Ege.
So you're done harassing me.
Is Güneş your next victim?
You decided to drop by like this?
-I miss Güneş. I thought I'd see her.
-Hmm.
Did you miss her too?
Kid…
Take your time.
I'll be waiting in the car.
You can drop by
whenever you want to, okay?
[Ege] We'll see.
No promises.
All this has been exhausting.
-[Güneş chuckles]
-[clicks tongue]
He really has missed you.
He kept asking about you.
[sighs] I missed him too.
I'll make sure to see him soon,
but he shouldn't come alone.
Maybe you could bring him.
I'm kind of busy lately,
but we'll sort something out.
Okay.
Didn't you want to have a word?
Oh…
I took care of that
since we didn't get to talk the other day.
-You took care of it?
-Uh-huh.
There is no need for me?
Not anymore.
So it's resolved.
Great.
If you've figured it out, I mean.
Okay then, Güneş.
-Deniz.
-Hmm?
That heavy box the courier left…
Can you have it collected at some point?
[clicks tongue]
Why don't you take a look inside
that heavy box?
I won't.
I can't. I can't open it.
Come and collect it.
Do whatever you want with it.
Fine, I don't want it either.
Throw it away.
Get rid of it. It's up to you.
Come and do it yourself.
I said it was heavy. It's this big.
-Besides, I can't be bothered.
-Then don't.
-I won't.
-Fine. Don't.
By the way, I hope you don't mind
me bothering you, Güneş.
[huffs] Enough already.
Enough. Exactly.
Have a nice day.
[sighs]
Someone has left us a house.
Pervin texted you.
You probably never saw it.
A lonely woman left us her house
in Cappadocia.
She left it to you, not me.
Sorry, to Mr. Alpha and you.
[sighs]
Yes, but she has a condition.
To claim the house,
we must convince the lawyer
that we are still together.
Hmm.
But we aren't.
How is that going to work out?
I was thinking…
What if we took a few photos?
-Then saw the lawyer there…
-We're back to where we started.
I've told you a million times.
I don't want anything to do with
this influencer stuff.
And you will never make me
lie to a lawyer I haven't even met.
What does that even mean?
It's important to me, okay?
Besides, what harm can a few photos do?
Is it that hard? What's so wrong?
-A few photos?
-Yes.
-Fake ones.
Hmm.
All right then. Let's give it a shot.
Let's see if we can fake it.
What? Did you forget how to hug?
[♪ romantic music playing]
I remember how
to hug you very well, Güneş.
How should we do it? You tell me.
Like this? Huh?
[no audible dialogue]
[music continues]
Okay, fine. Okay.
There. See?
It's not the same
after you break up, right?
It was a mistake to ask you for help.
Deniz.
Yes?
[footsteps approaching]
[music ends]
He's playing with me.
I'll show you how this game is played.
Darling, it's no game.
He's madly in love with you.
Don't you get it?
Oh, he's already dumped the girl.
What else do you want?
[clicks tongue] Yes.
How do you know he broke up with her?
Did we receive intel on that, Özgen?
Because I just heard about that from Ege.
Wait a minute! Hold on.
You're still in touch
with Deniz's buddy Hakan.
[Beren] Give us a break, Güneş.
What dealings could we ever have
with his lousy buddy Hakan?
You wait. Just wait.
You know me.
I wouldn't turn a head for him.
Özgen? Tell me.
[inhales sharply]
We missed one detail.
Over there. You two hugged over there,
but you didn't kiss.
-Is that it?
-Don't change the subject. Tell me.
[gasps]
Oh, okay.
[scoffs] I'm a terrible liar anyway.
Wait. I mean,
why do we have to stop seeing Hakan
just because you broke up with Deniz?
I don't understand.
Is that what you're implying?
Wow. Fine then.
When you say "we,"
do you mean we're friends with Hakan?
Friend…
-Let's not call it friends. Fine.
-Hmm.
[Özgen] Um…
We're affiliated at a professional level
with Hakan.
-You meant "you" are affiliated.
-Yes, Beren. Fine. I am affiliated.
What is the nature of this affiliation?
Care to tell us, Özgen?
Huh?
[sighs]
Let's say we help each other out
on certain issues.
[partner moaning, panting]
[sighs]
-[Hakan breathing heavily] Oh.
-[chuckles]
-[Hakan sighs]
[door unlocks]
-[door opens]
-[Özgen] Hello.
Honey?
Gee!
You ordered fast food without me?
What a bastard. And there's nothing left.
I can't believe it.
Hakan? Darling?
Hakan?
Hakan? [gasps]
Hakan, what the hell? Who is she?
I can explain.
What is there to explain? Tell me.
Is your name Hakan?
-Jerk.
-Ouch!
Tell me, Hakan. Speak up, asshole.
[chuckles]
[chuckles] Take them out to
a fancy restaurant, for heaven's sake.
I don't know, cook something nice.
I don't get it at all.
How can they buy into a fast food date?
It beats me.
Why do you have to yell,
calling me an asshole?
What's wrong with you?
I got slapped for it.
That surely hurt. I lost it there briefly.
I don't know.
I got carried away with the role.
I know the ropes now. That's why.
-But I was amazing. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
I asked you to come after I texted you.
You were early.
Really?
Well, it seems you were early too.
No. It was just fine.
Really? Fine.
[laughs] You men get hyped up so easily.
Fine. Don't get upset.
I was running late,
so I thought I'd drop by.
Come on. So where is
my signed romance novel?
Um, I couldn't find it on my last trip.
Geez, Hakan!
Hakan, listen up! If you blow the deal,
I'll never come again.
I'll never save your ass.
Then you'll have to spend the whole day
with those chicks like in romance novels.
No. I… No worries.
I'm going to London next week,
and I'm sure I'll find it there.
I've got this.
Send me a list
if there is anything else you want.
I'll forget if you tell me now.
-A list?
-Yeah.
Okay, I will.
I'll let you off this time.
You made me sit on this dirty bed.
Ugh. Change the sheets.
Now I'm really curious.
I won't be able to sleep.
What did you tell this girl your name was?
[laughing]
Tell me. Tell me.
-I'm not telling you. I won't.
-[laughs]
Well, that's it.
[scoffs] I'm all flushed now.
I mean, we talk occasionally.
Sometimes he calls me for things.
You know.
What kind of things?
[Beren] Oh, she freaks me out sometimes.
It's a very gross friendship at that.
[exclaims]
This… The fact that you detest everything.
Have you guys ever heard the term
"friends with benefits"?
-[Güneş laughs]
-[Beren sighs]
Friends with benefits
is nothing like that, honey.
-No, it's not.
-[laughs]
Yeah. You know everything.
Wait. Stop right there.
Forget everything.
-And I mean everything.
-Hmm.
You're a rational woman.
How can you do this to another woman?
Sweetie, let's not waste time on that.
For one thing,
nothing about me is rational. [laughs]
-Indeed.
-Well, excuse me.
Um. Secondly, I'm sorry, but it's obvious
that Hakan is not marriage material.
I can see it in his eyes.
Women should also be able to get it.
Well, she's finally making sense.
I mean, women can't be fooled so easily.
-Sure.
-[Özgen] Well, boo-hoo.
What did Deniz's girlfriend Umay do?
She had her claws deep into him.
I'm sorry, but that's the way it is.
[sniffs]
So her name is Umay?
So you also talk about this stuff
with Hakan?
[sighs]
Dear, I…
I should go. [sighs]
See you, girls.
Okay, Güneş.
-Can't you shut up for once?
-I goofed up.
-Shit.
-[scoffs]
[sighs]
[children clamoring]
Ege, are we done here yet?
Wait. Let me try out
that new slide over there.
Okay, make it quick.
I need to get back to work, okay?
Okay, I'll get back right away.
Okay, toddlers. Off the floor!
[Deniz] First date.
The guy is very tense.
He can't stop talking.
The girl actually likes the guy,
but she's holding back.
Playing hard to get.
The poor guy feels like he has to talk to
avoid awkward silences. Blah, blah, blah.
He's sweating, but…
Now, look at him carefully.
He's worried that he's talking too much
on their first date.
You know, it's not cool.
-That's how it is.
-Hmm?
[Deniz] Uh-huh.
-[chuckles] Right.
-What?
[chuckles] Actually, they've been together
for a while now. Really.
In fact, the girl bought
that sweater he's wearing.
She has taste.
I bet she can even
bake birthday cakes for him.
And the guy is this type.
So, when the girl comes home from work…
-Uh-huh.
-…he asks, "How was your day, darling?"
-The guy? [clicks tongue]
-Hmm.
-He is.
-No way.
Their friends will turn up any minute now
for a celebration.
[group] ♪ Happy birthday, Yağmur ♪
♪ Happy birthday, Yağmur ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-Wow.
-See?
-Spot on. Again.
-Uh-huh.
-How do you do it?
-[group applauds]
-You wait.
-Hmm?
[Deniz] Uh-huh. Um.
Right.
-Aha.
-Them?
-Oh, don't point. That's so rude.
-[scoffs]
[Deniz]
They've been married for forty years.
Pops enjoys a drink on the balcony
of their summer house.
She likes serving fruit and appetizers.
Her favorite thing is
to dunk bread in her appetizers
while keeping him company.
So at ease. What a great relationship.
[Güneş sighs]
What?
-Hmm?
In fact, they are the ones
who met recently, Deniz.
-No way.
-Yes.
Oh, come on.
They met recently.
They occasionally meet at that park bench.
-They both speak of their past…
-Hmm.
…and share their solitude
like the simit halves in their hands.
Do they also write poetry?
They do. They may be
writing a poetry book, all right?
Oh, for God's sake.
Really. They meet here now and then.
They spend a few hours together.
Then they both go back to their homes.
Yeah. You'll see.
[no audible dialogue]
[Deniz] Good God. Gosh!
[laughs]
Do you realize you can
see into the future?
Can I?
Oh, that's why you're so interested
in fortune telling.
-You know what?
-Hmm?
-What about us?
-Us?
How do we look from the outside?
Oh. [chuckles] Are you sure?
-Why? Is it bad?
-No. Fine, let me think.
Go on.
All right, I'll try.
Hmm. Wait, let me think a little.
Do that. Take a sip and then tell me.
All right.
[inhales sharply]
-The girl is the orderly type.
-Uh-huh.
She has taste. An eye for detail.
She cares about the guy.
She's the possessive type.
[chuckles] To the extent that
she often controls the relationship.
-But because the guy is so dominant…
-Yes?
-…she does it subtly.
-Oh, really?
So much so that the guy thinks
he's in control of things. [chuckles]
Scandalous.
It's a passionate relationship.
It started suddenly.
Yes.
What about the guy?
-The guy?
-Uh-huh.
-He's madly in love with the girl.
-Yes.
So, is that it?
[scoffs] That's him in a nutshell.
-[chuckles]
-What a disgrace!
[laughs]
Is that it?
Well, yes. In brief.
You give all that detail
about total strangers.
Can't you say more than
a sentence about me? Shame on you.
-What? The guy is in love.
-Really…
-He's in love. That's it.
-In love. That's all?
Uh-huh. Nothing else.
-Nothing?
-He's just blinded by love.
I get it. Nothing more?
Madly in love. Let's see.
Ow! He's burning. [laughs]
-[laughs]
-All right.
[children clamoring]
[piano playing]
Private account
[phone buzzes]
REMINDER
DINNER WITH BORAN
Boran.
I guess it's my turn to apologize.
Why?
Because your post branded me as Mr. Alpha?
You saw it, right?
I did.
What you did…
How to put it?
You're right to be angry.
This is the biggest step you've taken
in our relationship so far, Güneş.
What? Aren't you angry?
On the contrary, you made me very happy.
This is the first time
you have done something for me,
maybe for both of us.
-What?
-Listen.
You know what?
I don't care how others see it.
When I look at that photo,
I see the two of us.
-[chuckles] I don't know what to say.
-[chuckles]
I'm a little relieved,
but I still feel embarrassed.
No. You shouldn't. You're an influencer.
Of course, you will post about Mr. Alpha.
That's expected.
I would never want to see you
in a predicament, Güneş.
Remember that.
Thank you for being so understanding.
Not at all.
Um, I left you in a difficult situation
by asking you to wear that ring.
[chuckles, inhales sharply]
Now, at least, I know
how you felt back then to some degree.
Let's call it even. [chuckles]
Besides, when I saw the post…
I thought to myself,
"There is still hope for us."
We have a photo together.
That's something, right?
Boran, I guess I'm not the person you
expected me to be in this relationship.
Don't be.
Don't.
Be who you want to be.
As long as you're with me, Güneş.
Thank you.
[Güneş sighs]
It's been ages since
anyone has been so kind…
and understanding towards me.
Thank you.
[phone buzzes]
REMINDER
PODCAST LIVE AIRING
I should be going soon.
I have to make it to the podcast.
Would you like me to give you a lift?
[door unlocks, opens]
Honey?
I'm home.
Hakan?
Darling?
Oh, I wonder where he is?
Sweetie, can't you hear me?
Huh?
Honey?
Not here either.
Where could he be?
Is he here? [gasps]
Oh! Hakan, who is this girl?
Damn. I'm so shocked.
What are you doing?
How could you do this to me?
Who are you?
[exclaims] Who are you,
lying in my boyfriend's bed?
How will you explain this to me? Explain.
-I can explain.
-Go on, then.
You saw what you saw.
Hakan and I love each other.
Don't get in our way!
What?
Hold on a minute. I mean, we just met.
Isn't it a little too soon?
No, it's not.
Right… Now, you… I'm flipping out here.
I'll pull your hair out.
-I swear I'll do it.
-In your dreams.
-Who do you think you are?
-Uh-oh!
-Get lost.
-Uh-oh, girl.
I'll kick the crap out of you. Leave now.
-Who the fuck do you think you are?
-Fuck off!
-[glass shatters]
-[partner screams]
Psycho!
-[laughs] Oh, fuck.
-[door opens]
-Dude, what a nutter.
-[door closes]
Listen. Was that too harsh?
Telling her to fuck off and all? Huh?
-Özgen?
-What?
I swear, you are the only person
who could have pulled that off.
[laughs] Right.
I adore you, crazy bitch.
[chuckles] Keep your pants on! [scoffs]
I can't believe I'm fighting for
a man the same age as me.
[both chuckle]
What's that on your face?
What is it?
Let's go out for a nice meal.
I'll get dressed if you give me
some privacy. Let's have a bite to eat.
Oh, yeah. You're still naked.
I have things to do anyway.
[clears throat]
Um, I'll be off.
Tidy up a little while you're at it.
See you later.
What about food?
No.
[Deniz sighs]
Can you try calling this number again?
Tell his family that he's here.
Yes, sir.
You work too much, Deniz.
Oh, really?
-You're missing so much.
-Don't rub it in my face.
Be a good boy and wait here.
Mr. Rauf, I'm so sorry I'm late.
Something came up.
-Welcome.
-[Ege] Will you offer me something?
Strawberry milk, maybe?
Get used to it, Deniz.
Get some practice.
We're not hardwired to be fathers,
and what we do here is
a piece of cake compared to fatherhood.
Um…
-It's still too early for that. [chuckles]
-[laughs]
[Rauf] I've heard that before, Deniz.
You get tricked into it,
and the next thing you know,
you're changing diapers. [chuckles]
-I see you patched things up with Güneş.
-Huh?
I saw Güneş's post.
Um…
Güneş likes posting.
I saw you together at that event
where you made a speech.
Uh-huh. [clears throat]
Now, I have no problem with this,
but it's no secret
what people think of influencers.
I don't know how an influencer architect
will go down at our company.
[phone ringing]
Calling…
Yes. Shall we begin?
-[colleague speaking indistinctly]
-[phone buzzes]
Notification
New message - Pervin
[Pervin] Will we hear your voice
when Güneş talks about
Mr. Alpha on the podcast?
Um, Mr. Rauf. Please may I be excused?
-Hakan, can you cover for me?
-What's the matter? Not bad news, I hope.
No, no. It's not.
[clears throat]
Maybe at the beginning of a relationship…
[phone buzzing]
Calling…
Um. Maybe we will direct…
I'm here at the studio. Don't worry.
I'll be going on air soon.
Oh, great.
They'll broadcast it tomorrow.
You will be on the road.
I'll listen to it. I'll let you know
if any revisions are needed, dear.
-Okay?
-All right. Thank you.
[Pervin] Talk plenty about love, dear.
-Mr. Alpha and plenty of love.
-[bird] Love, love.
-All right.
-[laughs] Sweetie pie.
Listen to me.
Deniz didn't answer.
You're together, right?
[stammers] We…
We were together just this morning.
What does he think about
showing his face in Cappadocia?
-What does that mean?
-Oh, did I ruin the surprise?
Listen. Don't say a word.
You didn't hear it from me.
Keep it between us.
I won't talk to you otherwise. Okay?
I just texted him.
I asked if he would
say a few words on air.
Huh? What do you think?
-[sighs]
-Sensational, right?
Oh, Güneş, please.
He has this deep voice.
So beautiful. So sexy.
Oh, the way he talks. We must hear him.
Talk to him.
I'm sure you'll convince him. Huh?
Pervin, I really have to go.
Someone will meet you
at the airport tomorrow.
-[sighs]
-And I have little surprises for you.
You'll see when you get there. Okay?
Okay. Thanks.
Bye.
[phone buzzes]
I'm at the car park.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[Deniz sighs]
Will you ever come to your senses?
Stop criticizing me!
Enough.
I didn't ask you to come here.
It was Pervin's idea to reveal your face
and broadcast your voice.
-I'm tired of these games.
-So back off!
I just had to lie my way out of
an important meeting because of you.
[sighs] Oh, sorry. Mr. Alpha never lies.
Mr. this, Alpha that! Dang!
My life is guided by trust, damn it.
My rivals are just waiting for me
to slip up. Do you have any idea?
What? And this is my job.
It's my job to post
and be a guest speaker on this podcast.
Show some respect.
Respect? Sorry, but you posted
a photo as if we had made up.
Everyone is congratulating me.
God, give me patience!
What else should I expect?
Not everything is about you, okay?
-The world doesn't revolve around you.
-How is it not about me?
I doubt you even thought of me
before hitting send.
Oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't think of you
while I desperately sought a solution.
I'm sorry. If you calm down and listen,
I'll explain.
Go on, tell me. I'm dying to know.
Go on. For heaven's sake, tell me.
I need to sell the house
because I need the money.
I don't get this money thing at all.
Don't you earn a living
by being an influencer?
So you don't earn enough from publicity
and collabs as it is?
What's the point in trampling over
my career, my reputation, my trust?
Your career? Trust?
Are you lecturing me on trust?
I can't count on you
to come to Cappadocia with me.
That's why I had to post a photo
with another man in the first place.
-How can you talk about trust, huh?
-Are you really going to stand here
and tell me about the virtues of
being an influencer, huh?
Isn't that what destroyed
our relationship, Güneş?
[sighs] No, it's not, Deniz.
We broke up because you insisted on
using this as an excuse.
That's a lie.
We broke up because you couldn't
keep your promise to me, Güneş.
I… [sighs]
You went and promoted my rival
and made me an accessory.
Do you know that our photo is still
on display at that construction site?
How many times are we going
to talk about this? How many times?
I'm telling you, I didn't know.
I didn't know they were going
to use it like that, okay?
Fuck my career.
You wanted to be an influencer.
I told you explicitly that I didn't want
to show my face, not to involve me.
You chose your career over me.
And here you are, still at it.
I had to, Deniz.
I was abandoned.
I was alone.
Just like this Cappadocia thing.
Can we get this straight once and for all?
We weren't together because of this job.
We were together,
and you brought your job into it.
You think I like doing this? Huh?
I'm trying to find a solution.
I have to sell that house.
I need the money.
Do you think I'm comfortable selling
a stranger's house?
You think it's easy?
For God's sake!
Tell me how much you need,
and I'll give it to you.
Let's put an end to this ordeal.
-[sighs]
-What?
Go spend your money on someone else.
All I needed was you waving your money
and thinking it would solve my problems.
Now I've seen it all. Thanks a lot.
That's not what I'm trying to do.
I'm just offering a solution.
Not every problem is solved with
status or money, Deniz.
Yes, I need money.
Yes. I have to pay for
my sister's tuition fee.
So, I'm not earning that much.
Happy now?
[scoffs] I'm losing it.
Forget everything. Tell me…
How are we going to fake a relationship
and make it work? Is that even possible?
Right.
We can't be like that either, Deniz.
[sighs]
Exactly. I won't get involved in anything
I don't believe in.
I can't fake anything. Do as you please.
-[sighs]
-[engine starts]
[host] Shall we start, Güneş?
[sighs]
My guest today is
the famous editor Güneş Güner.
More recently, we know her from
her romance articles and as an influencer.
-Hello.
-[host] Hello.
So? Are your folks still fighting?
No fighting.
I need to ask you something.
That's why I'm here.
Go ahead, buddy.
They didn't answer
when you called them, right?
They had no clue I was even missing.
[breathes shakily]
[♪ pensive music playing]
[phone chimes]
[music ends]
[sighs]
Is my bag in there?
I said, is my bag here?
I don't see it. It's not here.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
-[sighs]
-What's the matter?
Why are you looking at me like that?
We'll be late. We have to leave.
[music ends]
[♪ playful music playing]
[♪ pensive music playing]
REMINDER - FLIGHT TO LONDON
16:00
[music continues]
-I'm waiting.
-Okay. I'm coming.
Let me sort these out,
and I'll be right with you.
[Boran speaking indistinctly]
[music continues]
[speaking indistinctly]
[music ends]
[phone ringing]
Calling…
-Hello.
-Hello, Hakan.
Something came up.
What? You're going to miss the flight.
Am I going without you?
The London flight won't wait
for you, dude.
I have to go now. Bye.
Well, what's so urgent?
[scoffs] Welcome, Deniz.
It's nice to see you too.
Thank you, I'm fine.
What about you?
I'm on edge.
This volatility is exhausting me.
One minute, we're good,
and the next, we're not.
Okay.
I wanted us to meet and talk, Deniz.
Is that so bad?
-Oh! [sighs]
-[chuckles]
Where were you, Boran?
I was on the phone.
I've got something to tell you.
-Yes?
-Are you excited about Cappadocia?
Yes.
Nice. Um…
I need to pay a quick visit
to the restroom.
Fine. Okay.
I guess it's the excitement, I don't know.
-Okay.
-I'm coming. I'll catch up.
It's right over there.
[sighs]
Deniz, what's the matter?
I'm flying to London.
I told you on the phone.
I know. That's why we met nearby.
That's not it.
What's wrong with you, Deniz?
Why are you so tense?
You've changed. Why?
Did you bring me here to interrogate me?
No, I'm trying to figure it out. [huffs]
I was angry with myself.
I thought I pushed you away.
I blamed myself.
This wouldn't have happened if I hadn't
brought up this issue with Güneş.
Deniz.
It wouldn't be like this, right, Deniz?
Oh, say something, please.
-Would you like to order anything?
-No, not now.
-Are we going to talk about Güneş again?
-[scoffs]
No, we talk about us.
I brought you here so we could talk.
Deniz, I'm here.
I'm not giving up on you.
I'm not going anywhere.
I want to be with you.
Do you feel the same way?
Fine. [sighs]
Well, since you asked.
You deserve an honest answer.
Let's put things straight.
I thought about it too.
You were right.
I'm still healing from the wounds
left by Güneş.
Nevertheless, I'm on my feet.
I've gotten used to living with it.
We're not together, just so you know.
I didn't approach her,
and neither did she.
She recently posted a photo.
I'm not in it.
So you saw the post too.
You know about the Mr. Alpha post.
I know, but let me be clear.
You're accusing me of something
I haven't done for the second time.
I don't owe an explanation
to anyone, Umay.
Where are you going?
To the restroom. Is that okay?
Sure.
[Güneş sighs]
Hello.
May I have an espresso, please?
[phone buzzes]
Güneş podcast is streaming,
you can listen to it.
We Sat At This Table
Güneş Güner
[host] My guest today
is the famous editor Güneş Güner.
More recently, we know her from
her romance articles and as an influencer.
-[Güneş] Hello.
-[host] Hello.
Can we cut to the chase
and talk about Mr. Alpha?
[chuckles]
We can talk about him
but don't expect to find out
more than is revealed in the photos.
Wait a minute. Hold on.
So how long will this mystery last?
I don't know.
[chuckles] I hope it lasts forever.
[host] Even sharing your ring
is enough to make you feel jealous.
It seems you really want to
keep him only to yourself.
I don't know how to respond to that.
-[bartender] Can I get you anything else?
-No, I don't. I don't want anything.
[host] Is your relationship similar
to the ones you portray in your articles?
Or is the influencer in you
fine-tuning the whole thing?
Honestly, I don't know if I count
as an influencer. I don't know.
I mean, I've recently received
collaboration offers,
but I don't see myself
as one at the moment.
-Where did the lady go?
-She left.
[Güneş] I think the chemistry of love
is different for everyone.
Love evolves into something else
as those molecules
blend through experiences
with our partners.
[host] Okay. You talk about
molecules, but how do you define love?
Define love?
It can be as serious as a history book.
I think it is also as fun as a playground.
There is this ride.
It's like stepping on a platform.
It spins around, making you dizzy.
I don't remember its name right now.
-[host] The merry-go-round.
-[Güneş] Yes, merry-go-round.
The merry-go-round.
[♪ romantic music playing]
[music continues]
I guess love feels like
a playground to me.
Maybe because I first fell in love there.
[music ends]
[host]
I don't want to discredit your idea,
but a merry-go-round
makes you sick after a while.
Like doomed relationships,
the ones that drag on.
-Men are like that sometimes, aren't they?
-[laughs] Yes.
But you're spot on. Yes.
That's when trust
in a relationship matters.
That's the seesaw.
One side is always higher
in relationships,
while the other is lower.
This balance changes constantly.
On that seesaw,
you have to feel sure that your partner
won't make you fall flat on your face.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[music continues]
[sighs]
[sniffles]
Boran, where are you?
[music continues]
[disconnect tone beeps]
[line rings]
-Hello. Welcome.
-Hello.
My friend is on his way.
He went to the restroom.
Sure.
Ms. Güneş,
why don't you proceed to the plane?
I'll take care of your friend
when he arrives.
-Is that okay?
-Sure. Thank you.
[airline worker] Have a good trip.
[huffs] Oh, Boran. Where are you?
Welcome.
[huffs]
How can Cookie sitting here bother you?
[flight attendant] Welcome.
Sweetie. My sweetie pie.
Look, we can sit here.
-Welcome.
-Hello.
[line rings]
[phone chimes]
Boran, I've called you many times.
Where are you?
Did you change your mind?
Uh, excuse me.
This seat is taken.
Oh, darling. Would you sit over there
so Cookie can sit here?
Look how much she likes it.
-Could you please sit over there?
-[chuckles]
It's very cute, but my friend is coming.
We're together so we chose these seats.
[scoffs] Oh, Cookie.
See what we have to go through.
I'm moving because I have to,
not that I want to.
[flight attendant, in English]
Boarding completed.
[in Turkish] What happened, huh? Doors are
closed, and your friend didn't make it.
He might.
Welcome, sir. You boarded just in time.
I do.
I never miss.
[♪ romantic music playing]
[Güneş] At the playground, you keep asking
yourself the same question.
Should I stay, or should I leave?
You can ask all you want.
Try to decide all you want.
It will never be a decision
based on reason.
Because you are at the playground,
and the game of love will always find you.
It will make you do things
you thought you'd never do,
turn your life upside down,
and make you forget breathing
and yourself.
It will sweep you off your feet.
And the real battle for love will begin
at that very moment.
[music continues]