reminder.
[gasps]
[Güneş] That's not what I told you, Özgen.
Honey, I'm only asking.
If that is where this story is going,
you can fast-forward
through the details in between.
Girl, I don't know why
I bother telling you anything.
Never mind her, honey.
You tell me. I'm all ears.
So, he boarded the plane
last minute and sat next to you.
Your hands were about to touch
when he chickened out
and leaned back?
Okay. Then what?
Then…
Then, he dozed off.
Oh… I-I was sure Deniz would
do something annoying like that.
My version of the story
was so much better, right?
Did you get the metaphors
about kissing while buckled up?
-You got it, right? You're a smart girl.
-[chuckles]
I mean, he's doing you a favor,
so he must make you suffer for it.
He has to include some drama
while doing his Good Samaritan gig. Pfft!
Men. What else do you expect?
Um… Is he with you now?
We just got to the hotel.
Oh, it's all so romantic.
Yeah, yeah. Very romantic indeed.
[sighs] Okay. So is that all?
Did he sleep the whole way?
No. He woke up for the celebration.
What celebration?
Start from the beginning.
For Ms. Güneş and Mr. Deniz.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
Pervin's doing.
Has it started already?
We're nowhere
near Cappadocian airspace yet.
Um. May I ask something?
Will this be your first time
in Cappadocia?
-Yes.
-Oh, how romantic.
[chuckles] Very romantic.
We need to take a video
of this for Pervin.
It's obvious she wants me to post it.
Fine, do it.
You need to be in it too, Deniz.
May I? Let me do it!
-Here, you hold the dog. Hold her.
-[Güneş] No…
-No.
-Hold the dog.
May Cookie make an appearance too, sir?
No, ma'am. No need. No need at all.
-[mumbles] She's really doing it.
-Um.
Why is he hiding his face?
Don't be embarrassed, son.
Don't be shy. Look here.
-Why is he hiding?
-It's better he's not seen.
It's not because he's shy.
Gosh.
Ma'am, would you please take this
Cookie of yours?
Please. Okay. Thanks.
Thanks anyway.
[passenger] Good God.
[Güneş] Again…
-I have to ask.
-Hmm.
Why is he hiding his face? Is he married?
No. He's not.
So, he is your boyfriend?
[Beren, on phone]
So, why do you think Boran ditched you?
I don't know. I keep calling him,
but he doesn't pick up.
Is this normal?
What if something happened to him?
Um… I thought maybe he saw Deniz
and backed out,
but…
He doesn't know Deniz, right?
Oh, whatever.
I'm glad he's out of the picture.
Maybe he didn't want to fake
being the other man anymore.
That's also possible.
I'm going to ask you something.
Is that all?
Is this all you have to tell us?
You with Deniz in the air.
Huh? Güneş?
[Beren] Güneş?
Honey, are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
We'll pretend we're lovers
in front of the attorney.
Then we'll tell him we want
to sell the house, and return. That's all.
Very well.
Make sure you keep us posted. Okay?
Yes, keep us posted.
Show me the house. I'm dying to see it.
[phone ringing]
-Özgen.
-[Özgen] Well done, sir.
Congratulations. It's done.
Did Deniz board the plane?
Oh, of course, he did.
I haven't been reading
romance novels for nothing.
Only this time,
I have no romance novels for you.
I also missed my flight
while trying to distract Boran.
Honestly, how did you pull that off?
-[Hakan] Make way! Make way!
-[driver] Sir.
-You can't stand up. It's forbidden.
-Excuse me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sir.
Hey, be careful. You almost ran me over.
I wasn't at the wheel.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Get your hands off me.
Unbelievable.
Go on, please.
If you don't know how
to drive a buggy then don't.
Unbelievable.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
Güneş?
Ms. Güneş has boarded.
Aha. Great.
Uh, ticket…
It was on my phone…
It's not here.
May I please see your ID and your ticket?
Um. I'm Boran.
Boran Saygun.
I can't let you through without an ID.
It's procedure, you say.
That's your job, sure.
Hold on. I'm so sorry.
[phone buzzing]
Güneş
is calling…
[Özgen] You took his phone?
Are we the mob, Hakan?
We're not the mob.
We're a romantic gang.
I can't believe you.
What could I have done?
It was a spur-of-the-moment thing.
I'll return it.
It's not like I stole his phone.
Oh. Hold on, hold on. Deniz is calling.
I'll call you back.
-Yes?
-Huh, Hakan.
Did you get my message?
I'm in Cappadocia.
Really?
And I missed my flight waiting for you.
I've got something to do.
I need to help Güneş.
I will return soon. Okay?
Talk to you later.
[coughs] Hello.
Oh, hello.
I'm your attorney, Mahir Temiz.
-Güneş Güner.
-Nice to meet you.
Deniz Derenoglu.
Oh, Mr. Alpha.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
I guess you'd like
to see Ms. Mesude's property first.
-Please.
-Mm-hmm.
By the way…
Forgive me,
but I need to ask you
some questions related to the will.
It's about your relationship.
I hope that is okay.
-Sure.
-[Mahir] Hmm.
No problem. No… That is absolutely fine.
There's nothing wrong
with our relationship.
-Why would there be?
-No.
I didn't think there was a problem anyway.
It's only that…
[chuckles] I don't know.
Looking at your photos,
I thought you guys would be
a more affectionate couple.
But I think you have
a more formal relationship.
Nope.
[chuckles]
[Mahir] Yes.
[whispers] Don't overdo it.
-Please, let's go.
-Very well.
I'll quickly grab my bag.
Certainly.
[breathes heavily]
-[Güneş] Hold my hand.
-Hmm?
Hold my hand.
What a genuine display
of affection that was.
Stop the banter. Keep walking.
Stop pulling me. I'm coming, Güneş.
-Walk in sync, will you?
-What?
Left foot, right foot. Come on.
You can't do it. Maybe hold my left hand?
-Aha. Now go.
-You're exaggerating.
See, it worked.
Stop it. Come on.
Hi. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
[Mahir] I met Ms. Mesude a year
after I moved here.
I came here every day for nine years.
She was a good person.
How long have you two been together?
-Two years.
-Two?
Uh-huh.
Two. It's not two.
Actually,
Deniz was courting me for two years.
We've been together for three to
three and a half years after that.
Yeah, two, three and a half, three years.
-Give or take.
-I see.
This is the house.
-What are you on about?
-Was I supposed to lie?
-[Mahir] Be careful not to slip.
-Yes, my love. Be careful not to slip.
Careful.
Here.
[Güneş chuckles]
Did Ms. Mesude live here?
[Mahir] Yes.
She was a very wealthy lady.
-An eccentric character.
-[chuckles]
[Deniz] We can figure that out.
She left her house to a total stranger.
-[Mahir] Hmm?
-[Deniz] Hmm?
Honey, I think the flight
here tired you out.
Um. No, dear.
The attorney mentioned how
eccentric Ms. Mesude was.
I was pointing out a fact.
The house is expensive, but it has buyers.
So, can we put it
on the market immediately?
[Deniz] No, you can't.
Dear, can we talk about
this privately at home later?
Dear, can we talk later?
[mouthing] What are you doing?
If you want to see the house,
feel free to look around.
We can then proceed to the next step.
Ms. Mesude's itinerary as per her will.
-[both] Itinerary?
-Uh-huh.
We… We weren't told about an itinerary.
We only know about the house.
Will there be a ceremony or what?
[chuckles]
As I pointed out,
Ms. Mesude was quite eccentric.
[Mahir] Hmm. Um.
[murmurs]
-What's happening?
-I don't know.
Ah.
And this is a letter from
Ms. Mesude to the lovers.
[Deniz] Uh-huh.
For you. Here.
Sure. Thank you.
Since you're lovers.
Um. [clears throat] Uh-huh.
-My love.
-Hmm. Darling.
My sweetheart.
Honeybunch.
-[whispers] Easy.
-Okay.
What letter? What is this all about?
Why do you agree to everything?
I don't get it.
We don't have to agree to anything.
Especially you.
Tell me, why did you come
with me in the first place?
Why did you join me if you
were going to be so difficult?
You know I'm terrible
at playing tricks, Güneş.
As if I'm a pro at it.
I asked the bellhop if he had a girlfriend
and told him I had a boyfriend.
The poor boy forgot his tip
and dashed out of the room.
Stop overdoing it.
Do you think we can put the house
on the market tomorrow?
No, it's not going to be that easy.
Why?
The house is of historical value.
You can't do anything to it.
I'm telling you, it won't be easy to sell.
But consider yourself lucky.
You're here with an architect.
Yeah, lucky me.
I'm here with an architect.
Deniz, did you just come here
to help me sell the house?
Is there no other motive?
I wanted to help your sister out.
What other motive could I have?
I don't know.
[Deniz sighs]
[softly] Geez.
What are you doing?
I was hoping to take a shower.
I-I need to work on my article.
Get undressed next door.
Why? Am I distracting you?
Feeling confused?
Stare at the fairy chimneys
over there and start typing.
Do whatever you want, okay?
Do whatever you want.
I will do that.
[sighs]
[singing "Asktan Ne Haber"]
[singing continues]
[audience cheers, whistles]
[giggling]
We did it! [laughs]
We did good. Real good.
-Amazing. Huh? What do you think?
-It was very good. It was great.
-We didn't embarrass ourselves either.
-Right? I think everyone enjoyed it.
Yeah.
-Thank you.
-[Deniz] Bravo. Bravo.
-Bravo.
-Was it bad?
-You did quite well, darling.
-Don't be silly. It was very good.
-It was good, right?
I honestly didn't hear any of it.
You're up next.
-I'm singing too? No, she's joking.
-You will sing.
You will sing.
Everyone in here sings.
-What kind of rule is that? No way.
-You will.
[Beren] Listen.
We were thinking of leaving,
but I guess you're staying on.
Yes. Deniz will serenade me.
-[Beren] Seriously?
-Yeah.
[Beren] Uh-oh.
-[Deniz] Yeah.
-Why don't you do things like that, Ozan?
-Serenade?
-Yes. To me.
Me, serenading?
-Really?
-Yes.
[chuckles]
I'm bored.
Let's go.
-Fine. All right then. Let's bail.
-[Ozan] It's best we go, bro.
-Give me my bag, dear.
-[Ozan] Here.
-Kisses for you all.
-See you.
Sorry, man.
Good night.
This guy is such a buzz-kill.
Exactly.
I mean, the more I see him,
the more I like Deniz.
No, don't say that.
I can and I will. I'm leaving, too.
I will find myself a man
who will serenade me.
-[laughs]
-You guys are so boring.
-Good luck.
-Oh, see.
[laughs]
Oh, come on. Sing.
It's really not my thing. I can't sing.
You can. What if we found a song you like?
I'm telling you, I can't.
Please, you didn't even look. Come.
You choose, you sing.
I'm a great listener. Let me listen.
-You want me to sing for you?
-Sing for me.
-Should I?
-Which song?
Let me pick one.
-Surprise? All right.
-Surprise.
Can I get another one?
[bartender] Sure thing.
[singing "Saz Mı Caz Mı?"]
[singing continues]
Wow, you can sing.
Come, let's sing together.
It's no fun alone. Come over.
Come on. Stop playing around.
Don't do this.
Ooh!
You're turning me on, baby.
[patrons gasp]
[patron] Come here!
[groans]
[Ms. Mesude] Dear Güneş.
If you are reading this letter,
it means that I've
already become a flower.
I've become rain.
I've become one with the valley.
Thank you for coming.
As my end nears, I found solace
in your writing and in your love affair.
The skilled people of this land
have passed down their prowess
to future generations.
Or, lent a hand, if you will.
I have always believed that
the ability to love is also a skill.
I see that you not only have that skill
but also inspire others.
That is also what you did for me.
In my final moments of despair,
you rekindled my dying hopes.
-So, I wanted you to have…
-…my most precious possession.
My antiquated house.
But before that, if you agree,
I'd like to take you on a short journey.
This will be my way of defining love
to you, just like you do in your articles.
[Ms. Mesude] I am confident that your love
will give life to this place
and that you will see love
from my perspective as you proceed.
I will reach out to you
with a letter at every stop.
I hope you take this trip.
Mesude.
Güneş.
[phone ringing]
[sighs]
-Mr. Rauf.
-Deniz.
What business do we have
with houses in Cappadocia, Deniz?
I understand you inquired
about the heritage status of one.
Um, yes. Well.
I mean, I wanted to get some advice
from our guys about this inheritance case.
I heard that you didn't
go to London, Deniz.
Uh… More like I couldn't.
Unfortunately, I missed my flight,
so I postponed it.
Deniz, listen.
I told you at the last meeting.
Your private life is your own business.
I'm fond of Güneş, too.
You're my most experienced architect.
I want to trust you on this London job.
Um, of course, Mr. Rauf. You can.
You can trust me.
Then I won't ask you what was so
important that you postponed the meeting.
Time is not on our side.
If you say so, I guess I don't need
to call you about it again.
Like I said, you can trust me.
Okay, Mr. Rauf.
Okay. See you.
Okay.
[sighs]
Here goes.
Shall I come over?
I'm coming. I can't hear you.
Okay. I'm coming.
[no audible dialogue]
[Özgen] I'm coming.
-[Hakan] …would be better.
-Really?
Hakan.
Özgen.
Who is this woman?
Özgen, calm down.
Um, excuse me. What's going on?
Who are you?
What's with the attitude? I don't get it.
-Özgen.
-Özgen, what?
Don't you dare call me Özgen. Shut up.
Tell me her real name now,
or I'll have to start name-calling.
You are so rude.
Are you juggling two women?
I can't believe
what is happening right now.
[Özgen]
What's done is done. That's too bad.
Get up and leave already.
I'm sorry, but I won't let you use him.
You're such a cheap bitch!
Sorry, but I can't build a future with
a man who dates women like her, Hakan.
Beste, wait a minute.
-Beste--
-Beat it, Beste. Stop dawdling.
Make it quick, Beste.
[laughs] That was great.
Özgen, what have you done?
I genuinely liked her.
-What?
-Özgen.
What did you do, Özgen?
[exhales heavily]
Why were you making those faces, then?
You beckoned me in.
I was telling you not to come in.
Not to come in? You beckoned me.
I saw you from over there.
Okay, fine. Let's go and explain.
Let's tell her it was all a sick joke.
Actually, let me do it.
Don't you dare. What will we tell her?
My buddy Özgen waits close by
to cut my dates short
when the women are boring, eh?
What excuse could there be?
No, we can't tell her that.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Uh-oh. Why am I the one apologizing here?
Why should I be sorry?
Didn't you hear what she called me?
Well, you were the one name-calling.
Beste was different.
Hmm.
Oh, Beste was different, huh?
Are you on her side?
Özgen, I said I liked her.
What don't you get?
You liked her?
Congratulations.
You ruined everything.
I rarely like someone.
She was nice.
Now she's gone.
[sighs]
[knocks on door]
[door opens]
Aha, Deniz.
Mesude gave us
some addresses in her letter.
I wish she had given us the title deed
and saved us all this trouble.
-Are you all right? Is something wrong?
-I'm fine. Just fine.
Which addresses?
Her will states that we
must visit these addresses.
I guess it's some kind of itinerary.
As a couple.
She probably wanted us to visit them
as a couple, Güneş.
Weren't we supposed to sell
the house and go back?
Deniz, she has left us a house.
We owe her that much, right?
Güneş, be honest with me.
How long will we keep playing
a stranger's game?
Yes, I realize you have things to do,
but I want to go through with it.
I'm not comfortable
acquiring the house as it is.
At least we'll honor a few wishes.
What's wrong with that?
I get it,
but how long will these games last?
Listen. Let's tell the attorney that I'm
an architect and sell the house.
What about that?
What about this?
You stay here, and I go alone.
[sighs]
All right, wait up.
I'm coming.
I'm coming with you, please wait.
[lounge pop-style music playing]
[Hakan] Mr. Boran?
-Fikret, right?
-Um, yes. I'm Fikret.
Where's my wallet?
Um. Here.
I'm sorry. There's been a mix-up.
I'm no pickpocket.
Really?
How much?
How much for what?
You found my phone and wallet.
How much do you want? Tell me.
No. You've got this all wrong.
That's not the case.
Enough with the games.
You're terrible at it.
Name your price. I'll pay you.
Pretending to bump into me and all.
It was all staged.
What is all this about?
Bro, are you asking for trouble?
Look, I brought you
your stuff in good faith. Stop it.
Oh, really? Who knows what you're up to?
Maybe you looked me up on the Internet.
You saw I was wealthy,
and now you're here to milk me.
So, you don't know
I'm the son of a media mogul.
Yeah, right.
The Good Samaritan to the rescue.
What are you talking about?
I don't give a damn
about who you are, man.
-Listen here.
-What the hell?
Now my girlfriend is alone in Cappadocia.
She went without me all because of you.
I missed my flight too.
Where were you going?
London.
More lies. What were you doing
in the domestic lounge then?
Um. I was trying to get to
international departures.
Yeah, right. Pfft. Unbelievable.
Whoa. Are you counting your money?
What? I thought money
wasn't an issue, Fikret?
-Boran.
-Huh?
Seems you're trying to pick a fight.
You want me to punch you in the face?
What kind of person are you?
Look!
[instructor] One hand on the inside,
the other on the outside.
That's how you hold it.
Now, pull up.
Please help her. She looks so clumsy.
I doubt she can do it.
In-In here… Throw it in here.
-It's okay if it gets a little messy.
-[instructor] Release your foot.
Take it aside for now.
-[Deniz] Do that.
-[instructor] Don't leave it spinning…
Bring it up. Excellent.
Can't you see it? It's all wavy.
As if yours is straight.
-Leave me alone.
-It's quite smooth.
Now you've totally messed it up.
There.
-See.
-[speaks indistinctly]
-My goodness.
-What if I do this, huh?
[instructor] Ms. Mesude's letter.
Thank you.
[dial tone]
She's not answering.
-[Hakan] Who isn't answering?
-She's not.
Who isn't answering?
Huh?
Güneş. My girlfriend.
Doesn't she care
what happened to me, Fikret? Huh?
What? Well, I don't think so.
I saw 15 missed calls from Güneş on there.
Why didn't you answer?
You should have told her you took
my phone at the airport by mistake.
Well, you could have called your
girlfriend before counting your money.
[sighs] Fikret.
[chuckles] Man.
Hmm. Come closer.
Listen up.
Now comes the crucial question.
You…
When was the last time you did something
for someone, expecting nothing in return?
Though I doubt you would do
anything of the kind.
Or has someone ever done
something for you expecting nothing?
Aha. Of course.
Sure.
If someone is doing something
without any expectation,
it means they care about you.
Take me, for example.
I care about Güneş so much.
Right.
They care.
Come closer. Closer, I said.
One more thing.
What about this?
Just one word…
Is it enough for you to go out
of your way to help her?
Or would someone rush
over to you in the middle of the night
to save you from another girl?
-Right?
-Of course.
If you find someone like that,
you treasure her, Fikret.
It's important.
You're right, man.
I let Özgen down.
Huh? It happens, bro.
No one is perfect.
[stammers, chuckles]
Take me, for example.
Do you know where I proposed to her?
-At a retirement home.
-No way.
-Don't rub it in.
-Dude! [laughs]
A terrible choice. Really.
[sighs]
Wait. Hold on. I'm going.
I'm going to Cappadocia.
I'm going to propose again.
Yeah. Get out of here.
I'm going.
-We'll be in touch, buddy. Okay?
-Sure thing.
-Well, take care.
-[Hakan] Keep in touch.
[thuds]
["Back To The River" playing]
Some guy.
[song continuing]
You can't be serious.
Come on, please.
[Güneş] Okay, okay.
This is the place.
Oh.
Isn't it stunning?
Really.
[song continuing]
-[guide] …these fairy chimneys--
-Hello.
Hello. Welcome.
…were formed by erosion.
Others suggest that lava
from Mount Erciyes was
carved by wind
and water over the centuries.
[song stops]
Ms. Mesude's letter for you.
Thank you.
[sighs]
Won't you open it?
Ever since I received the first letter, I
have wondered if I'll end up like Mesude.
Are you afraid of becoming rich enough
to leave a house to a total stranger?
[sighs]
No. Of being alone.
So alone that you leave your house
and all your memories to a total stranger.
You aren't alone. You have me.
What happens when we return?
Won't we go our separate ways?
[breathes deeply, sighs]
Mesude is so eloquent.
Won't we eventually get off
the hot air balloon we're traveling in?
Come on. Let's first jump in one
and remember how it feels to fly.
That was a metaphor.
Is that the gist you got from it?
Wait.
[song reprises]
[sighs]
Are you serious?
[Deniz] I'm dead serious.
So, we're really doing it.
[Deniz] Exactly.
You're opening up to this adventure.
Sure.
Wait.
Excuse me. Isn't the flame too strong?
[Güneş] Never mind that. Just look around.
I'm pretty sure it would still ascend
even if you dialed it down a little.
It's all part of the show.
What's the big deal?
-I don't get it.
-Oh, you're so grouchy.
Look around you.
You can't deny the beauty of the scenery.
[flame roars]
See that? It's incredible.
[Deniz] It really is.
[romantic music playing]
[music continuing]
[dance music playing]
Hi.
You look amazing.
Thank you.
You're not bad yourself.
Let me remind you that Mahir
will have his eyes on us tonight.
No doubt.
I'm sure that's why we're guests of honor.
Have you seen him? Where is he?
He's over there, flirting with someone.
Check out Mahir's moves.
Has he found someone?
That's nice.
Maybe he'll leave us alone tonight.
We could do with it.
Wow. That's love over there.
Oh, seriously?
Pe-Pervin. That's Pervin.
-Who?
-Pervin is here. Pervin!
[whoops] Surprise.
Oh, excuse me.
My darlings.
What's up?
We're fine. You?
Do you know each other?
We met thanks to you. [chuckles]
We kind of got closer while
organizing your trip.
We're just as surprised.
Next thing we're texting
and sending photos to each other.
-[Mahir] What about it?
-Sensational, right? [laughs]
What kind of photos?
[Güneş] Pervin?
-[Pervin] Hmm?
-[clears throat]
Mahir still thinks we are a couple, right?
Aren't you?
I hear you're together all the time.
The inseparable couple, huh?
-Well, yeah.
-Aw. Fingers crossed for us.
Listen. You also found inspiration
for the article.
-Not bad, right?
-[chuckles]
Love is such a beautiful thing, guys.
It's beautiful.
Time for a refill?
-Oh, go on.
-Huh.
-Well, see you later.
-See you.
Have fun.
-Something--
-To drink, maybe?
Margarita?
I'll get it.
That way.
[music changes]
Planning on wrecking this place as well?
I don't want any trouble tonight.
The night is long, Güneş.
You are full of surprises.
Trouble is my middle name, Deniz.
Come on then.
Up for a dance?
I'll hold your hand so you don't fall.
I won't. You'll catch me.
["You're In Danger" playing]
[patrons cheer]
[song continuing]
Bravo!
Bravo! Bravo!
[song ends]
[Güneş] Some moves you've got.
Hopefully he thinks we're lovers now.
So this was a show?
Was it about appearances?
No.
I'm saying I'm glad we're here.
We can go back to Istanbul
tomorrow if someone is waiting for you.
There is someone I've been
meaning to part ways with.
If we stay any longer,
we will see the hot air balloons
at dawn on our way to the hotel.
Then let's do that.
Seriously?
[chuckles] I'm serious and very drunk.
All right then.
Let's see the hot air balloons drunk.
I have a confession.
I won't remember it tomorrow
because I'm so hammered.
[chuckles]
Okay.
I was hoping you would come.
I'm glad you did.
Then I have a confession too.
I listened to the podcast.
[sighs]
Won't you say anything?
You've already listened
to what I have to say.
You had no problem talking to the host
and all those listeners.
Oh, Deniz. Where is this going?
Is it about other people
in our lives again?
No, no. It's nothing like that.
I didn't mean that. Um…
I loved it. A lot.
I mean, I really liked the podcast.
Thank you.
This may be the first time you've
appreciated something I've done.
[chuckles] So, where is this going?
Me not approving what you do again?
-Really?
-[chuckles] No.
That day at the park.
I will never forget tonight,
just like that day at the park.
[phone buzzing]
BORAN
-[button clicks]
-[buzzing stops]
[clears throat]
We really got caught up in this game.
We convinced the attorney.
Mesude's game is over.
We can go back to Istanbul today, huh?
-Deniz, hold on.
-Uh… What should we…
Let's sleep on it.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
I'll take the couch.
Get some rest. Good night.
Deniz.
[sighs]
Wait up. Can we talk?
Güneş. Um…
I'm not up for it right now.
Can we talk later?
[passenger] So he is your lover?
Why did you come, Deniz?
I wanted to help your sister.
You declined. So, here I am.
I wanted to be with you.
I'm here.
[Boran] Güneş.
Boran.
[tense music playing]
I didn't want you to be alone.
What's wrong?
Aren't you happy to see me?
I told them we were lovers,
but they didn't believe me.
Please can you get the keys to our room?
I'm so exhausted.
[tense music builds]